这是二零二零年河北省初中毕业生升学文化课考试英语试卷听力部分。
听力部分。
共有五道题。
第一题至第四题为选择题，
第五题为填空题。
做题时，先将答案答在试卷上，在听力测试结束后，再将答案转答到答题
卡上。
现在。
听力试音时间。
试音到此结束。
第一题，听句子，选出句子中所包含的信息。
下面你将听到五个句子，每个句子读两遍，
请你听完句子。
的第二遍朗读后，从各小题所给出的
三个选项中选出包含所听信息的选项。
第二题，听句子，选出该句的最佳答语。
下面你将听到五个句子，每个句子读两遍，
请你听完句子的第。
二遍朗读后，从各小题所给出的
,B,Jack,B Please bring your passage to school and read it in class tomorrow morning.
三个选项中，选出该句的最佳答语。
第三题：听对话和问题，选择正确答案。
案。
下面你将听到五组对话和八个问题，
每组对话和问题读两遍。
请你听完对话和问题的第二遍朗读后，从各小题所给出的
三个选项中选出正确答。
请听第二组对话，回答第十二题。
请听第三组对话，回答第十三题。
请听第四组对话，回答第十四、十五题。
请听第五组对话，回答第十六至十八题。
三亚.
三亚?
三亚。
第四题：听短文和问题，选择正确答案。
下面你将听到两篇短文和七个问题。
短文和问题读两遍，请你。
听完短文和问题的第二遍朗读后，根据所听内容，从各小题所给出的
三个选项中选出正确答案。
请听第一篇短文，回答第十九至二十一题。
Got it? number 19.
Who is probably talking?
Question number 20.
What is the speaker trying to do?
is the speaker trying to do?
Question number 21.
What do the children have to do tomorrow morning?
请听第二篇短文，回答第二十二至二十五题。
What the children have do the children The will be on June the 15th.
It's going to be lots of fun.
It'll be held in the Red Sun Park.
The competition will begin at 6 o in the evening.
And it'll finish at 8 o
All the dancers must wear white clothes.
No other colors.
Everyone will do four different dances.
To attend the competition,
you need to complete a form.
Call us here at double seven five one two three four.
And we'll post you one.
We'll also send you some more information about the competition.
A special hello to our young listeners.
We have an exciting competition for you.
Do you love dancing?
Are you good at it?
Are you a middle school student?
If your answers are yes, make a note of this.
competition will be on June the 15th.
It's going to be lots of fun.
It'll be held in the Red Sun Park.
The competition will begin at 6 o in the evening.
And it'll finish at 8 o
All the dancers must wear white clothes.
No other colors.
Everyone will do four different dances.
To attend the competition, you need to complete a form.
Call us here at double seven five one two three four.
And we'll post you one.
We'll also send you some more information about the competition.
Question number 22.
Who can take part in the competition?
can take part in the competition?
Question number 23.
When is the competition?
Question number 24.
What color should the dancers choose for their clothes?
Question number 25.
What do the dancers need to do to attend
What do the dancers need to do to attend the competition?
number 25. Read Dear Mr.
第五题，听短文填空。
下面你将听到一篇短文。
短文读两遍，请你听完短文的第二遍朗读后，根据短文的内容和提示，在
信息表中相应的横线上填入所缺信息。
I got the information in the local paper.
And I'm writing to say that I'm interested in a summer position in your gift shop.
My name is Jim Green.
I'm 18 years old.
And I'm studying math at a university.
I was born in Canada.
And I came to England two years ago.
I sold cakes in a store last summer.
But this year, I'd really like to work in a gift shop.
I'll be able to work every day from July to September.
Looking forward to your reply.
Yours sincerely, Jim Green.
Dear Mr. Black, I got the information in the local paper.
And I'm writing to say that I'm interested in a summer position in your gift shop.
My name is Jim Green.
I'm 18 years old.
And I'm studying math at a university.
I was born in Canada.
And I came to England two years ago.
I sold cakes in a store last summer.
But this year, I'd really like to work in a gift shop.
I'll be able to work every day from July to September.
Looking forward to your reply.
Yours sincerely, Jim Green.
Thank you for I
听力部分到此结束。
预祝同学们取得好成绩。